about 10 years before, under the guise of elevator renovations.
For all three of the buildings.
The shafts gave us access to all the columns and concrete supports.
We used this sprayable explosive.
When I first saw it, I was like,
This is a real James Bond shit.
The hardest part of the job was wearing a respirator the whole time.
We could barely see and couldn't take them off.
Because of all these bastards.
Whatever we sprayed it on turned to dust in the day of the event.
There was so much molten material left that one firefighter said it was like,
Looking at a river of lava.
It was in the spring of 2000 that we installed the first of the two hummingbeacons in some pyro.
Ran out a whole floor.
They didn't even question where the money came from.
We just said we'd make you a little art project.
The other beacon was a little harder to plan.
But we had a friend at Marcia McClellan who told us that
Peony was spun on the floor below and it could go.
And we almost did it without a trace.
But the new guy decided to take a group photo on the last day.
We forgot to cover up the labels on a box of dead mirrors.
The planes were actually the easy part.
They were fully remote controlled just.
We couldn't trust those errors to fly a Cessna.
Let alone a full-size airplane.
Everyone made money that day.
And no one questioned why owners didn't show up to work.
Or why everyone didn't get the exclusive pager warning.
The most suspicion anyone caused was Zim.
Waiting till a couple of weeks before the big day to move out.
We even told the owner.
They're gonna know that you knew.
We all thought they'd catch on to Larry.
He waited till a month before to put the place in his name.
And created the first of its kind insurance policy for the maximum payout.
Lucky guy.
I asked him what his alibi was and he said his wife scheduled it.
An annual German collegeist appointment.
The Masagas didn't give a fluff that day.
Even if they got caught, they knew they would just get sent home.
The events of the day were even painted on the sides of their vans.
And some got spotted by a grandma while dancing on top of the parking lot.
When they were supposed to be filming.
Then they got caught again on the George Washington Bridge before they could set one of their vans off.
We had to make a cop actually change his story when he went on the radio and said he found
some explosives in the van.
They get arrested and screened at the Palestinians in the real enemy.
They get caught with plane tickets to different parts of the world.
One of the five dudes.
And 4700 in cash stuffed up his ass.
They gave our team a sweet bonus incentive in the form of a couple truckloads of gold.
Felt like we were in a die-hard movie.
Now we're, we get notified that they have the blow thing early.
So we are forced to abandon the trucks on a service time longer five.
Then we moved on to seven to wipe some financial records towards the place.
We find the deputy director of the emergency services department wandering around the command center.
He says his name was Barry.
I tell him.
You kind of get out of here, man.
I asked if he's alone.
He said it's just him and a friend left.
The building's janitor, Jose Gonzalez.
Ask where Jose is.
He says he's downstairs.
I say we're exactly downstairs.
He says Jose's on the first floor.
So I start to leave him out.
As we make it down the stairs it felt like.
47 cruise missiles hit the lobby.
We took another staircase and Barry unfortunately sees too much.
Tells the news about it.
So we had to make him change his story on the scene in a few months later.
I'm shot him in the neck with a heart attack pellet.
Finally I get back to the main scene.
I find a rookie cop who looks lost.
I hand him the passport and say.
I found the sun in the rubble over there.